(Watch on KonFlix.vip)
(Phone Vibrates)
Yes, Mom?
Have you arrived in Phuket yet, dear?
Yes, I'm here.
Why didn’t you tell me?
I was worried, you know.
Mom...
I just got off the plane.
As long as everything worked out, that’s all that matters.
And don’t forget.
Don’t do anything risky.
You don't have to be worried, I'm already here.
And also, nothing is gonna happen, Mom.
Don’t forget to go to the shrine like the feng shui master told you.
Have you met Sang yet?
Hey Mom? I gotta go now.
Actually, life here isn’t as bad as I’d imagined.
Hey! You!
How could you step on another man's crown jewels?
I... I'm so sorry!
Wait!
You're not even thinking of apologizing?
You!
You got no manners!
I already apologized.
But you're the one that didn't listen.
At that volume, how would I have heard you?
Well, I already tried apologizing.
You just didn't listen carefully.
Well, next time, could you please try to speak louder?
That would be great.
Then...
next time...
please listen carefully.
That would be great too.
Serves you right!
Hey, sis.
Where have you been?
Well...
I got here since early morning.
I thought coming home would be too boring..
so I went to the beach.
The beach?
Hey!
What are you getting riled up about?
A girl being this loud, when will you ever find a boyfriend?
Sang.
And didn't you say you were going out with a client?
That's because I was waiting to pick up Kim, Dad
I was waiting for ages,
I called, and he didn't pick up.
Next time, if you're going anywhere, tell us!
We got actual jobs to do!
Well..
..no one told me that someone was picking me up.
Seriously, Kim..
why'd your mom send you here?
About that..
Mom told you already you, didn't she?
The quarter life crisis?
Women are so gullible.
These kinds of things..
if you don't believe, then don't talk ill of them, Dad.
These rich people types are all superstitious.
And another thing..
I don't think being a woman means you're gullible.
Even amulet dealers are men, aren't they?
Siw!
Will there be a day where you don't argue with me?
Act like the daughter I raised you to be!
Why does my life have to be like this?
No son, can't rely on either of my daughters..
If there’s anything, be there to help your sister, understand?
It's okay..
I can do it myself.
Look at my daughters...
Siw!
Take your cousin to his room!
Let's go go.
What you looking at?
You look good now that you're older.
What's with you?
Well, when you moved to Bangkok, I was still really young
I can barely remember anything
not even what your face looks like.
Alright, alright...
I'm gonna unpack.
Wait...
What else?
You're really here for the inheritence?
Just kidding!
Don't worry..
I'm only here for another 364 days.
Once the year is complete,
I'm going back to Bangkok.
That's good.
Because if you're gonna mess with Dad and Sang,
I think you should take your time and work,
.. that might be easier.
Then...
What do you think I should do?
Live stream and talk to myself day by day?
Kinda like..
Hello!
It's Siw!
You...
know that I'm an influencer?
Are you following?
Well..
No.
I was just... scrolling through.
Kay!
I'm outta here!
I'm actually pretty famous!
(Phone Vibrates)
Yes, Mom?
Uncle told me you’d arrived but still refused to come home.
Do you know how worried you’re making your mother?
Mom...
you don't have to worry, okay?
I can take care of myself.
Once the year is up...
I'll be back to take care of you again.
Mom?
I love you.
- Daiji..
- Yeah..
Prepare more food tomorrow, okay?
We got guests in almost 10 rooms.
- Almost fully booked
- Okay, can do.
Make some Kanom Jeen too, and also..
fish balls...
maybe some lobster, around 10 kilos...
Oh, okay...
And where did Tao Sor go?
Probably...
out to draw outside...
Huh?
He's drawing outside?
Who did he go with?
Who let him go?
I already told him..
to wait for me to get the stock ready first
but he wouldn't take it
said he could go himself.
He wouldn't let me tell you too!
Tao Sor!
Yes?
Where have you been?
Umm...
I was outside
I told you already, right?
If you're going anywhere, you need to tell me.
Okay, okay...
go paint.
How you been, Tao Sor?
You took the car for a trip?
This is Dr. Kluen
he's been taking care of your conditon all this time.
Why...
...do I feel like I've seen this in my dreams?
These pictures you drew...
must be your dreams you remembered from each night.
And...
...as for the drawings with clear faces
most likely came from you drawing
and wanting to remember them
so you drew them out in detail.
Why...
..can't I remember anything?
It's okay, Tao Sor.
You can't remember today,
but tomorrow, you might! Who could tell?
How long have I been like this?
That's not important, Tao Sor!
And...
..will there be a day that I can remember?
But... whatever.
Even if I knew, I'd just forget it all tomorrow.
Isn't it enough for you to be happy with today?
The space for memories...
your family will be filling in those blanks, for what you need to know.
Whether or not you will remember,
I want to let you know
that everyone loves you and cares about you always.
Okay.
There's a large ship booking today, Dad
I was thinking that I'll go too.
Let Gim take care of that!
Put him to work for once
I'll tell him myself.
Don't bother, Dad.
It's my job, I can do it myself.
What about Siw?
Probably not awake yet?
Both of my daughters...
each such a case.
Your nephew's also the same
I can't see much difference.
I've got it!
I'm going to do a 1 day trip here.
What kind of trip?
Taking tourists...
to come learn local cooking.
I'll be back, sis.
Daiji,
could you help me try this?
- Can do!
Woah!
This is on point!
Woah, so delicious!
Good!
Delicious!
You remembered?
That I don't eat spicy foods in the morning.
Oh...
Daiji told me to get Dry Boiled Rice for you.
So I see.
Menu, Sir.
Tell your chef to go ahead.
Anything that your chef makes best.
Excuse me!
Could you bring the owner here?
If you had anything, you can tell me.
I want to talk to the owner.
Okay!
Um, excuse me?
Are there any problems with the food?
You're the owner here?
I'm the one who made this dish for you.
If there's anything you don't like, you could tell me.
So you're a chef, huh?
Good!
Will you be interested in doing a project with me?
Is there anything going on?
So...
I tasted the food here and I feel like the flavour is...
...so delicious!
It made me think about when I was here with my brother when I was young.
So I want to hold a 1 day trip here,
so I can bring tourists to come learn how to cook.
This way, everyone would be able to know your food as well.
If you want something, please come talk to me this way
I'm the one who makes all the decisions here.
We can just talk here!
You've seem to have lost your manners
coming here, doing some weird test
and being delusional thinking you'll do this and that here.
And what do you think?
This is probably better than your resort
in case the tourists who come like it here,
and decide to stay here.
Daiji!
What's up?
I'm letting Daiji look after this project.
No.
I need the chef who made this dish for me
be the one in charge.
What do you think?
Are you interested in joining this project with me?
Hey, you don't know anything
better not to get involved.
If you won't take my offer of having Chef Daiji teach,
then you're welcome to leave.
Daiji.
Take Tao Sor to go rest.
Okay.
Let's go!
Wait!
I'd rather hear the answer from the chef's own mouth.
I'm going to do this project.
Good! In that case,
Next week I'm going to bring my first tour group here.
As for you...
Next time,
give me a banger.
But really...
Letting Tao Sor try something new,
is a good thing, you know?
But I'm afraid that kid is gonna become a problem for Tao Sor.
Why would you worry?
We've taken care of Tao Sor for 10 years already!
We've been through dark moments so many times.
Something as small like this, we'll be able to get through.
Kim!
After being outside all day,
what have you brought back?
I think..
you, can start finding clients for my tour.
Because, I've found a place that teaches cooking.
It's real hot, I'm telling you.
I'm sorry?
Who said I'd find clients for you?
If you're gonna do something yourself,
then be able to do it all!
For the only male heir of the clan,
something like this shouldn't be difficult.
Okay!
Just wait and see...
(Phone Vibrates)
Yes, Mom?
Have you eaten yet, dear?
Yes, I have.
Oh! Mom?
I went to eat at a place today.
So delicious!
It tasted like my childhood, where..
Uh...
let's just say
it still can't beat the food at Bangkok.
There's tons of great places everywhere in Bangkok, you don;t have to fly down here to Phuket.
Have you gone to the shrine yet?
Yes...
..in about..
2 -3 days I was thinking of going.
The deity there's kind and easygoing, right?
Then..
I'm going to freshen up and go to bed, okay?
That's all.
Good night, Mom.
Good night.
Tao Sor.
My name's Talay
I'm your brother.
Mom and Dad are waiting downstairs.
Get showered quick
I'll show you around the house.
Our family runs a resort.
Normally, you'll help out in the kitchen.
You might not remember,
but you make amazing Thai and Chinese food.
As for the other cuisines, Chef Daiji will be in charge
and he'll help you with everything.
So today there will be a tourist couple coming to learn cooking with you.
Huh? With..with me?
It's okay, no need to worry.
Today's menu is Mie Hokkian,
a menu you could make with your eyes closed.
Isn't that right?
I do know how to make it,
I don't know how to teach.
What should we do?
This way, follow me!
So ladies and gentlemen, welcome to Siam Cuisine.
The exclusive honeymoon kitchen.
Um...
I might have to ask to cancel for today.
Wait, hey.
How could you do this?
My clients are already here.
All the ingredients are laid out and prepared, no?
But our chef isn't ready yet.
If you want Tao Sor, it has to be another day.
But if you're set on today,
I'll have Chef Daiji be the one teaching.
One minute please.
Hey, you.
We're all grown up
have some responsibility.
We talked that day, didn't we?
You made an agreement with me.
Why are acting like you don't remember.
Hey, sir.
It's the same either way.
Could you not make this a big deal?
It's okay.
I'll teach.
Okay, that means we're clear?
Sir, Ma'am? Please come inside.
You slice off the shallot,
I want to you to cut it by yourself.
Because.
I want you to stand
the smell of the shallot.
This will make it taste better.
Could you slice and look at the camera?
With confidence.
Are you even a real chef?
Can I get a confident expression?
Look at the camera too, this one.
Ah, and slice, you have to slice too.
Blood!
- Tao Sor!
- Come here.
Is it serious?
- Daiji, go get the first aid kit
- Okay.
Does it hurt alot?
Hold on for a while, okay?
You're good?
Tao Sor.
Go rest first.
We'll have Daiji take care of the rest.
Hey man.
It's just a little cut.
I think Tao Sor's still got it.
- Right?
- Hey.
What's your deal with Tao Sor?
Are you okay?
Yeah, everything is okay.
You know.
We actually came here to be taught cooking by you.
We were actually here last year, try your food, it was incredible, it was amazing.
So, we wanted to come back again and cook with you.
Yeah, I just wanted to cook some nice food for my boyfriend.
Do you remember last year when he complimented you?
You don't remember, do you?
It was only last year when we came.
I think everything is fine, it's okay.
He can continue teaching you.
And he remember you. Let's continue with the Padme Hokkien.
Next time, could you just
go with the flow first, understand?
Let me take a photo for you, cooking together.
Daiji.
I think Tao Sor's had enough, take him to rest.
Okay, come!
Apologies.
The chef is not usually be like this.
Maybe he is not feeling well today.
Tell you clients they can order anything
I'll take care of the charges.
As for the contract, I still cannot sign it.
I told you from the beginning that our chef wasn't ready.
Hey.
What are you doing here alone?
Don't you have class?
I went already.
Such a waste of time, learning who knows what.
Better to use the time making content.
What about you? What are you doing?
I'm just ...
..taking a stroll.
Just taking a stroll.
That was bad acting.
Like you'd know.
It's just..
I don't wann go back home yet.
I don't wanna deal with Sang's questions.
Which means,
today's trip wasn't good.
Aren't I right.
I shouldn't have went with that Precious Resort.
That Chef Tao Sor,
his skills are good, that's true
but unprofessional.
Chef Tao Sor...
Oh! The youngest son of The Pitch or something?
I've heard people talk,
that the youngest son had disappeared for a while.
And once he came back,
he didn't really go anywhere.
Some people have also said
he was harrased.
Other people say,
he drowned.
Until his brain wasn't normal.
But, no one's ever confirmed what the real story is
and his family doesn't say much either.
Really?
Would you want to get your fortune told?
Your business might blow up, you know.
No, that's enough.
Just being trapped her for a year because of a feng shui master's tellings
it's already driving me crazy.
- Stop. With the fortune tellers, stop
- Listen first!
This one's for real, I gurantee.
- No, no
- Hey!
That's why his luck's down, he hasn't even checked it yet.
Look, you.
Why are you sitting here alone?
I’m just sitting here watching the sunset.
Are you afraid of the ocean?
'll bring you out there. Trust me.
I've never been in the ocean before.
In that case, there might be another way.
I’ll be the one who becomes your memory